hourlyadprofit.com 2015-08-10

# Hourlyadprofit.com | REVOLUTIONARY PROFIT SHARING

Privacy Policy  
Below you can find the information regarding our privacy policy.

This privacy policy sets out how HourlyAdProfit.com uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website. HourlyAdProfit.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.We should ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. HourlyAdProfit.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with the changes.

You agree that all information, communications, materials are unsolicited and must be kept private, confidential and protected from any disclosure. Any information, communications and materials contained herein are not to be regarded as an offer, nor a solicitation for spend in any jurisdiction which deems non-public offers or solicitations unlawful, nor to any person to whom it will be unlawful to make such offer or solicitation. All the data giving by a member will be used privately and not disclosed to any third parties. HourlyAdProfit.com is not responsible or liable for any loss of data that happens by your fault.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect online.

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
